Guide to the Harry Randall: Fifteenth International Brigade Films and Photographs ALBA.PHOTO.011
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series E: Miscellaneous, 1938-01-1939-09
  - Photo Unit #: E1031 British Battalion assembly at fiesta, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1810)
    (Moscow Number: 5/184/23)
  - Photo Unit #: E1035 Football game at British Battalion fiesta, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1807)
    (Moscow Number: 5/184/20)
  - Photo Unit #: E1037 High-jumping competition at British Battalion fiesta, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1811)
    (Moscow Number: 5/184/24)
  - Photo Unit #: E1047 Race in mounting machine guns at British Battalion fiesta, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1812)
    (Moscow Number: 5/184/25)
  - Photo Unit #: E1048 Spanish soldier accidentally wounded at British Battalion fiesta, Marca, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1806)
    (Moscow Number: 5/184/18)
  - Photo Unit #: E1051 Assembly of British Battalion at fiesta, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1813)
    (Moscow Number: 5/184/26)
  - Photo Unit #: E1053 Major Edward Cecil Smith and Commissar Frank Rogers, undated (Box 6, Folder 11-1568)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/54)
  - Photo Unit #: E1054 Lincoln-Washington fiesta, 1938-07-19 (Box 1, Folder 11-0099)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/51)
  - Photo Unit #: E1055 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, 1938-07-19 (Box 6, Folder 11-1569)
  - Photo Unit #: E1056 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, 1938-07-19 (Box 6, Folder 11-1570)
  - Photo Unit #: E1057 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, 1938-07-19 (Box 6, Folder 11-1571)
  - Photo Unit #: E1058 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, boxing match, 2nd anniversary of outbreak of war, 1938-07-18 (Box 6, Folder 11-1572)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/46)
  - Photo Unit #: E1059 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, the winner!, 1938-07-18 (Box 6, Folder 11-1573)
  - Photo Unit #: E1060 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, Mike Pappas [Michael Papadopullo], 1938-07-18 (Box 6, Folder 11-1574)
  - Photo Unit #: E1061 Shot-put contest at Lincoln-Washington fiesta, 1938-03 (Box 1, Folder 11-0100)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/43)
  - Photo Unit #: E1063 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, 1938-07-19 (Box 6, Folder 11-1575)
  - Photo Unit #: E1064 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, foot race, 1938-07-19 (Box 6, Folder 11-1576)
  - Photo Unit #: E1065 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, three legged race, 1938-07-19 (Box 6, Folder 11-1577)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/50)
  - Photo Unit #: E1066 Lincoln-Washington fiesta, 1938-07-19 (Box 1, Folder 11-0101)
  - Photo Unit #: E1067 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, "Virginia item", 1938-07-19 (Box 6, Folder 11-1578)
  - Photo Unit #: E1068 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, 1938-07-19 (Box 6, Folder 11-1579)
  - Photo Unit #: E1069 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, 1938-07-19 (Box 6, Folder 11-1580)
  - Photo Unit #: E1070 Lincoln-Washington Battalion fiesta, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1581)
  - Photo Unit #: E1072 Marching to Brigade assembly (Lincoln-Washington Battalion), 1938-07-19 (Box 6, Folder 11-1582)
  - Photo Unit #: E1073 Marching to Brigade assembly (Lincoln-Washington Battalion), 1938-07-19 (Box 6, Folder 11-1583)
  - Photo Unit #: E1074 Marching to Brigade assembly (Lincoln-Washington Battalion), 1938-07-19 (Box 6, Folder 11-1584)
  - Photo Unit #: E1075 Marching to Brigade assembly (Lincoln-Washington Battalion), 1938-07-19 (Box 6, Folder 11-1585)
  - Photo Unit #: E1077 Marching to Brigade assembly (Lincoln-Washington Battalion), 1938-07-19 (Box 6, Folder 11-1586)
  - Photo Unit #: E1080 15th International Brigade Assembly, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, [marching in ranks], 1938-07-19 (Box 6, Folder 11-1785)
    (Moscow Number: 5/181/28)
  - Photo Unit #: E1081 15th International Brigade Assembly, 1938-07-19 (Box 6, Folder 11-1587)
    (Moscow Number: 5/181/26)
  - Photo Unit #: E1083 Brigade Assembly, Major José Antonio Valledor speaking, 1938-07-19 (Box 6, Folder 11-1588)
  - Photo Unit #: E1084 Brigade Assembly, Major José Antonio Valledor speaking, 1938-07-19 (Box 6, Folder 11-1589)
    (Moscow Number: 5/181/25)
  - Photo Unit #: E1085 Brigade Assembly, Major José Antonio Valledor speaking, 1938-07-19 (Box 6, Folder 11-1590)
  - Photo Unit #: E1086 15th International Brigade Assembly, 2nd anniversary of outbreak of war, 1938-07-19 (Box 6, Folder 11-1591)
  - Photo Unit #: E1087 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Marca, 1938-07 (Box 2, Folder 11-0512)
  - Photo Unit #: E1089 Lincoln-Washington Battalion building a foxhole, Marca, 1938-07 (Box 3, Folder 11-1204)
  - Photo Unit #: E1091 Luigi Gallo, John Gates, André Marty, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1592)
  - Photo Unit #: E1092 Chabolas [shelters] at Estado Mayor [Headquarters], 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1593)
  - Photo Unit #: E1096 Members of special Machine-Gunner Battalion of 15th army corps, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1594)
  - Photo Unit #: E1100 Town square, Asco, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1595)
  - Photo Unit #: E1102 Fascist prisoners, Asco, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1596)
  - Photo Unit #: E1105 Going to the front lines, Lincoln-Washington, 1938-07 (Box 1, Folder 11-0102)
  - Photo Unit #: E1107 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Estado Mayor [Headquarters], 1938-07 (Box 1, Folder 11-0103)
  - Photo Unit #: E1108 Lincoln-Washington Battalion first-aid post, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1597)
  - Photo Unit #: E1109 Lincoln-Washington Battalion first-aid post, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1598)
  - Photo Unit #: E1111 Lincoln-Washington Battalion first-aid post, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1599)
  - Photo Unit #: E1112 59th Battalion stretcher bearers at Gandesa, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1600)
    (Moscow Number: 5/186/8)
  - Photo Unit #: E1113 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, 1938-07 (Box 1, Folder 11-0104)
  - Photo Unit #: E1114 Lincoln-Washington Battalion observer, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1601)
  - Photo Unit #: E1115 Lincoln-Washington Battalion observer, Corbera, undated (Box 6, Folder 11-1868)
  - Photo Unit #: E1116 Lincoln-Washington Battalion observer, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1602)
  - Photo Unit #: E1117 Lincoln-Washington Battalion Machine-Gunner nest, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1603)
  - Photo Unit #: E1118 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1604)
  - Photo Unit #: E1120 Battalion Captain Milton Wolff, Lincoln-Washington, 1938-07 (Box 1, Folder 11-0105)
  - Photo Unit #: E1121 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Joseph Brandt, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1605)
  - Photo Unit #: E1122 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1606)
  - Photo Unit #: E1123 Lincoln-Washington Battalion members resting, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1607)
  - Photo Unit #: E1124 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1608)
  - Photo Unit #: E1126 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1609)
  - Photo Unit #: E1127 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1610)
  - Photo Unit #: E1128 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1611)
  - Photo Unit #: E1129 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1612)
  - Photo Unit #: E1130 [Soldiers firing rifles], 1938-07 (Box 3, Folder 11-1205)
  - Photo Unit #: E1131 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1613)
  - Photo Unit #: E1132 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1614)
  - Photo Unit #: E1133 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1615)
  - Photo Unit #: E1134 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1616)
  - Photo Unit #: E1135 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1617)
  - Photo Unit #: E1136 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1618)
  - Photo Unit #: E1137 Lincoln-Washington Battalion Lieutenant Aaron Lopoff and Lieutenant Rico Rusciano, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1619)
  - Photo Unit #: E1138 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1620)
  - Photo Unit #: E1139 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1621)
  - Photo Unit #: E1140 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1622)
  - Photo Unit #: E1141 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera [soldier, from back], undated (Box 6, Folder 11-1623)
  - Photo Unit #: E1142 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1624)
  - Photo Unit #: E1143 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1625)
  - Photo Unit #: E1144 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera [soldier, on ground], 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1626)
  - Photo Unit #: E1145 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera [machine gun], 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1627)
  - Photo Unit #: E1146 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1628)
  - Photo Unit #: E1147 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1629)
  - Photo Unit #: E1148 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1630)
  - Photo Unit #: E1149 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1631)
  - Photo Unit #: E1150 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1632)
  - Photo Unit #: E1151 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, machine-gun nest, Gandesa [5 soldiers], 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1633)
  - Photo Unit #: E1152 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, machine-gun nest, Gandesa, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1634)
  - Photo Unit #: E1153 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, machine-gun nest, Gandesa [4 soldiers], 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1635)
  - Photo Unit #: E1154 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, [7 soldiers,] Gandesa, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1636)
  - Photo Unit #: E1155 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, [soldier using] telephone, machine-gun company, Gandesa, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1637)
  - Photo Unit #: E1156 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, [two machine-gunners in trench], undated (Box 6, Folder 11-1638)
  - Photo Unit #: E1157 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, machine-gun company, Gandesa [soldiers at gun], 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1639)
  - Photo Unit #: E1158 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, machine-gun company, Gandesa [2 soldiers at gun], 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1640)
  - Photo Unit #: E1159 Lincoln-Washington Battalion Estado Mayor, Headquarters of 59th Battalion, 15th International Brigade, during attack on Gandesa, Mark Millman, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1641)
  - Photo Unit #: E1160 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Gandesa [soldiers walking up hill], 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1642)
  - Photo Unit #: E1161 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, stretcher bearers, Gandesa, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1643)
  - Photo Unit #: E1162 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Gandesa [soldiers and horses on trail], 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1644)
  - Photo Unit #: E1163 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Gandesa [soldiers and horses on trail], 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1645)
  - Photo Unit #: E1164 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Gandesa [4 solderis, one with bandaged head, on trail], 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1646)
  - Photo Unit #: E1165 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, stretcher bearers, Gandesa, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1647)
  - Photo Unit #: E1166 Lincoln-Washington Battalion stretcher-bearers, Gandesa, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1648)
  - Photo Unit #: E1167 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Gandesa [soldiers relaxing on ground], 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1649)
  - Photo Unit #: E1168 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Gandesa [trench?], 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1650)
  - Photo Unit #: E1169 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Gandesa, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1651)
  - Photo Unit #: E1170 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Gandesa [soldiers on ground], 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1652)
  - Photo Unit #: E1171 Looking toward Corbera [landscape, long view], 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1653)
  - Photo Unit #: E1172 Looking toward Gandesa [landscape, long view], 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1654)
  - Photo Unit #: E1173 59th Battalion, trench mortar, Gandesa, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1655)
  - Photo Unit #: E1174 59th Battalion, machine-gun nest, Gandesa, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1656)
  - Photo Unit #: E1175 59th Battalion, Gandesa [soldier with rifle, in trench?], 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1657)
  - Photo Unit #: E1176 59th Battalion, Gandesa [soldier aiming rifle, behind rocks], 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1658)
  - Photo Unit #: E1177 59th Battalion, water detail, Gandesa [two soldiers, with tins], 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1659)
  - Photo Unit #: E1178 59th Battalion, water detail, Gandesa [one soldier], 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1660)
  - Photo Unit #: E1179 59th Battalion, evacuating wounded, Gandesa [soldier on stretcher], 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1661)
  - Photo Unit #: E1180 59th Battalion, evacuating wounded, Gandesa [soldier on stretcher], 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1662)
  - Photo Unit #: E1181 15th International Brigade Sanidad [Health] post, Gandesa, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1663)
  - Photo Unit #: E1182 Lincoln-Washington Armory, Gandesa, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1664)
  - Photo Unit #: E1183 15th International Brigade, Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Gandesa [men at tunnle, or bridge, entrance], 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1665)
  - Photo Unit #: E1184 Observer, Gandesa, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1666)
  - Photo Unit #: E1185 Planes overhead, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1667)
  - Photo Unit #: E1186 Major José Antonio Valledor and Lieutenant [?] Julia, Gandesa, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1668)
  - Photo Unit #: E1187 Major José Antonio Valledor and Lieutenant Julia, Gandesa, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1669)
  - Photo Unit #: E1188 Captain Dunbar and Major José Antonio Valledor, Gandesa [with 2 others], 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1670)
  - Photo Unit #: E1189 Captain Dunbar and Major José Antonio Valledor, Gandesa [with two others], 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1671)
  - Photo Unit #: E1190 Captain Rollin Dart, Gandesa, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1672)
  - Photo Unit #: E1191 Morris Stamm and John Coon, Lincoln-Washington, Gandesa, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1673)
    Available Formats: Original Negative; Copy Negative; Print
  - Photo Unit #: E1192 Loading a machine-gun belt, Gandesa [2 soldiers], 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1674)
  - Photo Unit #: E1193 Patrick Roosevelt and Pete [?], with machine gun, Gandesa, Lincoln-Washington, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1675)
  - Photo Unit #: E1194 Abraham Copeland of Transmiciones [Transmissions], Gandesa, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1676)
  - Photo Unit #: E1195 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Gandesa, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1677)
  - Photo Unit #: E1196 Lincoln-Washington Battalion David (Red) Drummond, Nick Pappas, Eluard Luchell McDaniels, Gandesa, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1678)
  - Photo Unit #: E1197 Captured Machine-Gunner, Lincoln-Washington Battalion Gandesa, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1679)
  - Photo Unit #: E1198 Sergeant Guy Thorpe and Sergeant Max Bowers, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1680)
  - Photo Unit #: E1200 Cabo Narciso Gonzales, Adjuntant Lieutenant Jack Cooper, Jefe, Rafael Maltes, Commissar, Spanish M. E. [?] Company, Gandesa, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1681)
  - Photo Unit #: E1201 Herman (Gabby) Klein sleeping, Lincoln-Washington Company 3, Gandesa, 1938-08 (Box 1, Folder 11-0106)
  - Photo Unit #: E1203 David Lipton firing rifle, Lincoln-Washington, Company 3, Gandesa, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1682)
  - Photo Unit #: E1204 Lincoln-Washington Battalion Company 3, Gandesa, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1683)
  - Photo Unit #: E1206 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion Company 3, Gandesa, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1684)
  - Photo Unit #: E1207 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Gandesa, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1685)
  - Photo Unit #: E1209 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Gandesa, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1686)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/14)
  - Photo Unit #: E1210 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Gandesa, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1687)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/55)
  - Photo Unit #: E1237 Water tank, Corbera, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1688)
  - Photo Unit #: E1240 Cubans, Corbera, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1689)
  - Photo Unit #: E1241 Cubans, Corbera, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1690)
  - Photo Unit #: E1242 Sandor Voros, Miles Tomalin, Ernest Mahoney, Corbera, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1691)
  - Photo Unit #: E1244 Lincoln-Washington group, 1938-08 (Box 1, Folder 11-0107)
  - Photo Unit #: E1245 Alvah Bessie and Edwin Rolfe, Lincoln-Washington, 1938-08 (Box 1, Folder 11-0108)
  - Photo Unit #: E1246 Aaron Lopoff, Alvah Bessie, Rico Rusciano at Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1692)
  - Photo Unit #: E1247 Ernst Toller and David Roosevelt, Corbera, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1693)
  - Photo Unit #: E1248 Ernst Toller and David Roosevelt, Corbera, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1694)
  - Photo Unit #: E1249 Ernst Toller, 1938-08 (Box 1, Folder 11-0109)
  - Photo Unit #: E1250 Lincoln-Washington group playing cards, Corbera, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1695)
  - Photo Unit #: E1251 Lincoln-Washington observers, Corbera, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1696)
  - Photo Unit #: E1252 Lincoln-Washington positions at rest, Corbera, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1697)
  - Photo Unit #: E1257 Tony Pujol digging refugio, 1938-08 (Box 1, Folder 11-0110)
  - Photo Unit #: E1258 David Gordon, Maurice Miller, Edwin Rolfe, Corbera, 1938-08 (Box 2, Folder 11-0513)
  - Photo Unit #: E1259 Estado Mayor [Headquarters] group, runners, etc., Corbera, 1938-08 (Box 2, Folder 11-0514)
  - Photo Unit #: E1260 Estado Mayor [Headquarters] group, Thomas Norton in center, Corbera, 1938-08 (Box 2, Folder 11-0515)
  - Photo Unit #: E1262 Group from Williamsburg, New York, Lincoln-Washington, Corbera, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1698)
  - Photo Unit #: E1265 MacKenzie-Papineau Company, 5 citiations: Deszo Beke, Jose Asenci, Yaigve Lekto, Toivo Suni, undated (Box 6, Folder 11-1699)
  - Photo Unit #: E1268 59th Battalion, Company 2, citations: Luis Peraza, Lieutenant Geronimo Lopez, Pedro Aquilla Rio, Corbera, 1938-08 (Box 2, Folder 11-0516)
  - Photo Unit #: E1276 Salvador Plana, James Bourne, William Griffiths, Mora de Ebro, 1938-08 (Box 2, Folder 11-0517)
  - Photo Unit #: E1278 Some of the Commissariat, Mora de Ebro, 1938-08 (Box 2, Folder 11-0518)
  - Photo Unit #: E1283 Waiting to cross the Ebro, 1938-07-25 (Box 2, Folder 11-0519)
  - Photo Unit #: E1285 Building foot bridge across Ebro, 1938-07-25 (Box 2, Folder 11-0520)
  - Photo Unit #: E1286 Building foot bridge across Ebro, 1938-07-25 (Box 2, Folder 11-0521)
  - Photo Unit #: E1287 Building foot bridge across Ebro [carrying lumber], 1938-07-25 (Box 6, Folder 11-1869)
  - Photo Unit #: E1288 Building foot bridge across Ebro [sections of bridge piled on river bank], undated (Box 6, Folder 11-1870)
  - Photo Unit #: E1289 Building foot bridge across Ebro, 1938-07-25 (Box 2, Folder 11-0522)
  - Photo Unit #: E1292 Stretching the cable across Ebro, 1938-07-25 (Box 2, Folder 11-0523)
  - Photo Unit #: E1293 Stretching the cable across Ebro, 1938-07-25 (Box 2, Folder 11-0524)
  - Photo Unit #: E1302 Building the foot bridge, 1938-07-25 (Box 6, Folder 11-1700)
  - Photo Unit #: E1303 Stretching the cable across Ebro, 1938-07-25 (Box 2, Folder 11-0525)
  - Photo Unit #: E1305 Building the foot bridge, 1938-07-25 (Box 2, Folder 11-0526)
  - Photo Unit #: E1306 Crossing the Ebro [placing the lines], undated (Box 6, Folder 11-1877)
  - Photo Unit #: E1307 Building the foot bridge, 1938-07-25 (Box 2, Folder 11-0527)
  - Photo Unit #: E1308 Building foot bridge across Ebro, 1938-07 (Box 3, Folder 11-1206)
  - Photo Unit #: E1309 Building the foot bridge, 1938-07-25 (Box 2, Folder 11-0528)
  - Photo Unit #: E1312 Crossing Ebro by boat and bridge, 1938-07 (Box 3, Folder 11-1207)
  - Photo Unit #: E1313 Crossing the Ebro by boat and bridge, 1938-07-25 (Box 6, Folder 11-1701)
  - Photo Unit #: E1315 Crossing the Ebro by boat and bridge [landing in a boat], undated (Box 6, Folder 11-1876)
  - Photo Unit #: E1317 Crossing the Ebro by boat and bridge, 1938-07-25 (Box 6, Folder 11-1702)
  - Photo Unit #: E1318 Crossing the Ebro by boat and bridge [men walking to boats], undated (Box 6, Folder 11-1871)
  - Photo Unit #: E1320 Crossing the Ebro by boat and bridge[launching a boat, another in background], undated (Box 6, Folder 11-1872)
  - Photo Unit #: E1321 Crossing the Ebro by boat and bridge, 1938-07-25 (Box 2, Folder 11-0529)
  - Photo Unit #: E1322 Crossing the Ebro by boat and bridge, 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1703)
  - Photo Unit #: E1323 Crossing the Ebro by boat and bridge, 1938-07-25 (Box 2, Folder 11-0530)
  - Photo Unit #: E1325 Crossing Ebro by boat and bridge, 1938-07 (Box 2, Folder 11-0531)
  - Photo Unit #: E1328 Crossing Ebro by boat and bridge, 1938-07 (Box 2, Folder 11-0532)
  - Photo Unit #: E1333 Crossing Ebro by boat and bridge, 1938-07 (Box 2, Folder 11-0533)
  - Photo Unit #: E1336 Crossing the Ebro by boat and bridge[launching a boat, close-up view], undated (Box 6, Folder 11-1873)
  - Photo Unit #: E1338 Crossing the Ebro by pontoon bridge, undated (Box 6, Folder 11-1874)
  - Photo Unit #: E1340 William Allander and his truck after bombing, 1938-07 (Box 2, Folder 11-0534)
  - Photo Unit #: E1341 Bill Allander and his truck after bombing [with man unloading a box], undated (Box 6, Folder 11-1704)
  - Photo Unit #: E1344 Captured rifles, 1938-07 (Box 2, Folder 11-0535)
  - Photo Unit #: E1349 Corbera recaptured, 1938-08 (Box 2, Folder 11-0536)
  - Photo Unit #: E1350 Brigade Estado Mayor [Headquarters], undated (Box 2, Folder 11-0537)
  - Photo Unit #: E1354 Shelling near Lincoln-Washington positions, undated (Box 2, Folder 11-0538)
  - Photo Unit #: E1355 Shelling near Lincoln-Washington positions, undated (Box 2, Folder 11-0539)
  - Photo Unit #: E1358 Unexploded Shell, undated (Box 2, Folder 11-0540)
  - Photo Unit #: E1359 Drawing water at MacKenzie-Papineau [?] [donkey with several soldiers], undated (Box 6, Folder 11-1705)
  - Photo Unit #: E1361 Lincoln-Washington Battalion out for rest, undated (Box 2, Folder 11-0541)
  - Photo Unit #: E1362 Heliograf squad [3 men], 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1706)
  - Photo Unit #: E1363 Heliograf squad, 1938-07 (Box 3, Folder 11-1208)
  - Photo Unit #: E1365 Heliograph squad, Russell Stephens [3 men w/equipement], 1938-07 (Box 6, Folder 11-1707)
  - Photo Unit #: E1367 Heliograf squad, 1938-07 (Box 2, Folder 11-0542)
  - Photo Unit #: E1368 Doctor Julius Hene, Major Edward Cecil [?] Smith, Hamish Frazer, undated (Box 6, Folder 11-1708)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/43)
  - Photo Unit #: E1371 Brigade Estado Mayor [Headquarters], undated (Box 2, Folder 11-0543)
  - Photo Unit #: E1372 Washing up, undated (Box 2, Folder 11-0544)
  - Photo Unit #: E1374 William Van Felix and Ernest Amatniek, undated (Box 2, Folder 11-0545)
  - Photo Unit #: E1375 Lincoln-Washington wounded, undated (Box 2, Folder 11-0546)
  - Photo Unit #: E1376 Lincoln-Washington wounded, undated (Box 2, Folder 11-0547)
  - Photo Unit #: E1377 Lincoln-Washington wounded, undated (Box 2, Folder 11-0548)
  - Photo Unit #: E1378 Lincoln-Washington wounded, undated (Box 2, Folder 11-0549)
  - Photo Unit #: E1379 Lincoln-Washington wounded, undated (Box 2, Folder 11-0550)
  - Photo Unit #: E1380 Lincoln-Washington wounded, undated (Box 2, Folder 11-0551)
  - Photo Unit #: E1383 Loading machine-gun belts, undated (Box 3, Folder 11-1209)
  - Photo Unit #: E1384 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, undated (Box 2, Folder 11-0552)
  - Photo Unit #: E1386 Lincoln-Washington Estado Mayor [Headquarters], undated (Box 2, Folder 11-0553)
  - Photo Unit #: E1387 Lincoln-Washington Estado Mayor [Headquarters], George Watt and Major Milton Wolff, with others, at Gandesa Front, 1938-08 (Box 6, Folder 11-1709)